xploder.net 2011-01-15

# Xploder Privacy Policy | About Us | Xploder Online

### Xploder Privacy Policy

**Xploder Limited Online Privacy Statement**

Xploder Online recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of Xploder.net (XPLODER). We created the following policy guidelines with a fundamental respect for our users" right to privacy.  

**General**  
XPLODER uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure and to disclose such information only to responsible third parties after permission from the user.

XPLODER is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of websites to which we may provide links or the websites of our affiliates or advertisers.

 **Information Collected by XPLODER**  
XPLODER collects information about users during their registration for our newsletter and during their participation in certain activities on our website, including contests. When users request pages from our server, our Web server automatically collects some information about the users, including their IP addresses. These addresses are used by computers on the network to send the requested pages to users.

 **Use of Information**  
XPLODER does not reveal any personal information that users provide to us to any third party without their permission.

XPLODER uses users" IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. We also use it to gather broad demographic information about our users in general. We may combine demographic information supplied by a subscriber at registration with site usage data to provide profiles, in aggregate form, about our users and their preferences in the content of the site and advertising. We may share this composite information with our advertisers to help them better understand our services, but XPLODER does not give advertisers information about individual users of XPLODER.

XPLODER uses cookies to deliver content specific to users" interests and to honor their preferences. This information is used to assist us in creating a site that will serve the needs of our users.

 **Newsletters**  
Using e-mail addresses provided at registration or otherwise, XPLODER periodically sends out e-mail newsletters and promotional e-mail to our users about XPLODER and its advertisers. Users can indicate that they do not wish to receive e-mail information from XPLODER. Third parties will not contact our users through the use of our e-mail newsletter lists except through advertisements within the newsletters themselves. Users" contact information may also be used by XPLODER to contact the user when necessary.

 **Advertising**  
XPLODER may use user entered information in combination with site usage information to help display advertisements relevant to the users interest and navigation patterns. XPLODER may use cookies to help in tracking these patterns but does not store or collect personal data in combination with user supplied information.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, 

[click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

 **Public Forums**  
XPLODER makes message boards available to our users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

 **Children"s Guidelines**  
Although XPLODER does not specifically seek to obtain any information from children, there are certain areas of our website that children may visit. We urge children to only give us any information after they have discussed it with their parents.

 **Choice/Opt-Out**  
XPLODER provides users the following opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor, and upon request:  
Email:  

[unsubscribe](mailto:unsubscribe@gamezone.com) [at] xploder.net

 **Correct/Update**  
XPLODER provides users the following opportunity for changing and modifying information previously provided:  
Email support [at] xploder.net

 **Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with XPLODER, you can contact:

Xploder Webmaster

admin [at] xploder.net
